ILR School Building Dedication Miscellany /4206
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Building Dedication Miscellany
1945-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4206
1.44 cubic feet
1.3 linear ft.
Records, pamphlets, cassette tapes, clothing, memorabilia.
Files, pamphlets, audio cassettes, newspaper clippings, memorabilia, and clothing relating to the 1998 dedication of Ives Hall.
8051317
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Scope and Contents
This collections consists of files, pamphlets, audio cassettes, newspaper clippings, memorabilia, and clothing relating to the April 16-18, 1998 dedication of Ives Hall on Cornell's Ithaca campus.
Also held in this colleciton is an original copy of the 1945-1946 General Announcement on the founding of the New York State School Industrial and Labor Relations School.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4206 P: ILR School Martin P. Catherwood Library Photographs
Cornell University; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8051317
- April 17, 1998 Building Dedication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Stone paper weight commemorating building dedication.
- NYSSILR Cornell University, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  2 pamphlets about the ILR School.
- Cornell Chronicle, April 23, 1998 Dedication Articles Photocopies (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Building dedication materials, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Contains complete copy of the Cornell Chronicle (April 23, 1998), a hand out containing the lyrics for WHen I'm Gone by Phil Ochs, and an announcement for the All the Live-Long Day: A Folk Song Tribute to the World of Work (cassette tapes of this concert are boxes 2, 3, and 4).
- Constance Kheel, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Pamphlets of Constance Kheel's paintings.
- ILR dedication and Catherwood Library pamphlets, 1945, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Of note is a copy of the General Announcement on the founding of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations 1945-1946.
- ILR Clothes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  2 T-shirts; 1 Sweatshirt
- A folk song tribute to the world of work, 4/17/98 (side 1-2), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- A folk song tribute to the world of work, 4/17/98 (side 1, copy 2), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- A folk song tribute to the world of work, 4/17/98 (side 2, copy 2), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)